{
    "subject": "resource/Silas_Bryan",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Culpeper_County,_Virginia",
    "human_readable": "Silas Bryan was born in Culpeper County, Virginia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.963826596736908,
            "question": "Name the county where Silas Bryan was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9136824607849121,
            "question": "Where was Silas Bryan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9093882441520691,
            "question": "Is Silas Bryan from Virginia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9053484201431274,
            "question": "In what state was Silas Bryan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8348011374473572,
            "question": "What is the name of the place where Silas Bryan was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.634770393371582,
            "question": "What other famous people were born in Culpeper County?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5985671281814575,
            "question": "What is Silas Bryan known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4520551264286041,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Silas Bryan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3742864727973938,
            "question": "Is Culpeper County a well-known place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36059126257896423,
            "question": "Does Silas Bryan have any notable accomplishments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Silas Bryan was born in Culpeper County, Virginia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3561_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Culpeper County a well-known place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3561_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Silas Bryan?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3561_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Silas Bryan known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3561_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3561_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3561_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3561_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3561_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3561_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3561_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3561_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3561_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3561_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3561_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I found that the information provided supports the triple. Here is the JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe triple states \"Silas Bryan was born in Culpeper County, Virginia.\" This statement is explicitly mentioned in multiple documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3561/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3561/re-ranker-msmarco/65.txt). Therefore, the information in the documents supports this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Born: 1822-11-04 Culpeper County, Virginia\" for Silas L. Bryan, which supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}